http://www.specialtyfood.com/specialty-food-association/about-us/privacy-policy/

You are here:
Home
»
Specialty Food Association
»
We Are Committed to Your Privacy
The Specialty Food Association (“SFA”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. When you attend an SFA event and/or visit the SFA websites specialtyfood.com and my.fancyfoodshows.com (each a “Website” and together, the “Websites”), we help you maintain control over your personal information. We will collect, store and use your personal information solely to support and enhance your relationship with us and our members. For example, we may use your personal information to share products and services of the SFA and its members, partners and sponsors, and to update you regarding trade news, SFA events and offerings. The SFA does not sell your personal information. We share your personal information only with your consent, as required by law, or with companies that help the SFA fulfill its obligations to you, and then only with companies who share the SFA's commitment to protecting the confidentiality of your personal information. You may contact the SFA at any time with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You may also ask at any time to see the personal information you have given us and request correction or deletion.
We only Ask for Specific Types of Personal Information
In a few areas on our Websites, online support tools, and occasionally at our events, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your Website experience and/or the event, to assist you with technical support issues, or to follow up with you after your visit. Information we may request includes your name, email address, phone number, address, type of business, job function or title, product and services offerings, payment information, customer preference information, and similar personal information. If we ever ask for significantly different information, we will inform you.
As a registered user of the Websites you may set up a personal dashboard on the Website and you may enter personal information and preferences on your dashboard in order to enhance your Website experience. You may also set up a user profile for the purpose of participating in interactive forums with other registered users. You may enter personal information in your user profile in order to identify and describe yourself to other participants in the interactive forums.
We only Use Your Personal Information for Limited Purposes
The information you provide will be used solely to support your relationship with the SFA and its members. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on the Websites, and alert you to trade information, upcoming SFA events, and other SFA services. The SFA may enhance or merge your information collected at the Websites with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.
The information entered on your personal dashboard is used solely to enhance your event and/or Website experience, your ability to obtain information regarding the SFA, SFA members and their products, and to communicate with the SFA and SFA members. The information in your user profile is meant to identify and describe yourself to other participants in the interactive forums, and therefore may be viewed by other registered users. SFA does not collect or use the information entered in your user profile for any purpose other than to administer the interactive forums.
The SFA may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, or other legal action, or if the SFA reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect the SFA, its members, or the public.
Your Participation is Optional
Your participation in any portion of SFA events and/or the Websites or use of any Website functionality that calls for you to provide personal information is entirely optional. Any time after you provide the SFA with personal information, you may elect not to participate in functionality offered through SFA events and/or the Websites or request the SFA to delete any personal information. As a registered user of the Websites, you may choose at any time to terminate your registration on the Website or change or delete personal information on your dashboard or in your user profile. Any personal information entered on the dashboard or in your use profile and so deleted will not be retained by the SFA.
You May Choose not to be Contacted by SFA or its Members
Periodically, we may send you information about our various services, trade shows and events, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only the SFA or agents acting on behalf of the SFA under obligations of confidentiality will send you information. If you do not want to be included on the SFA's marketing list, simply inform us at the time you provide us with your personal information. You may at any time opt-out of SFA's marketing list or update your information by contacting SFA's Customer Service at membership@specialtyfood.com.
As a registered user of the Websites, you may elect to allow SFA members to contact you via the Websites’ onsite messaging system. You may at any time opt-out of this election by switching off this functionality on your personal dashboard.
SFA Will not Disclose Your Personal Information without Your Consent
Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) will not be given or sold to any third parties for use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of the SFA that have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of your information and use it solely for the purpose of performing services for the SFA.
The information of registered users entered on the personal dashboard will not be disclosed to any third parties, and may not be viewed or accessed by SFA members or other Website users. If you elect to contact, and/or be contacted by, an SFA member via the Websites, the SFA member will be provided with your name, but not your email address or other personal information. Any such contact by an SFA member will be made solely through your personal dashboard, unless you and the SFA member agree to contact each other through means other than the Websites.
The information of registered users entered in the user profile will not be disclosed to any unauthorized third parties by SFA, but may be viewed or accessed by other registered users.
Cookies and Web Beacons
In order to help enhance the performance and functionality of the Site, we utilize session, persistent and third-party “cookies” that store a small piece of data on a users’ computers and collect certain information about the users’ visit to our Site. We also use cookies to understand users’ browsing and buying activities so that we can measure the success of online advertising campaigns we run on the Site. Our Site and our emails may use web beacons or other tracking technologies (either directly or from our partners), along with cookies, to determine if a user has visited a particular website. These beacons aid in providing more relevant advertising to the user, as well measuring the success of an advertising campaign, but provide no personally identifiable information.
Cookies are small text files that web servers typically send to users’ computer when they visit a website. Cookies are stored as text files on users’ hard drive, and can be accessed by web servers when the user visits a website or views an advertisement.A session cookie is a cookie that stores information as a user is using the Site but is deleted once the browser session is finished.A persistent cookie is a cookie that stores information as a user utilizes the Site and stores and uses that information in connection with future visits of the user to the Site.Third-party cookies and/or web beacons are cookies or web beacons provided by our technology and/or advertising partners.Any third-party cookie or web beacon that we authorize for use on the Site only collects that information described below for the same stated purposes as if we were directly collecting the information.For a third-party cookie or web beacon, the third-party will have access to the collected information in order to provide us with information or services to enhance the performance and functionality of the Site.
The cookies and web beacons we use collect non-personally identifiable information about users of the Site, including: IP address, browser used to access the site, date and time, the URL of the page being loaded, users who have visited a particular website(s), any previously assigned cookie identification (a unique identifier assigned to a user to identify repeat visitors), browser window size, the geographic location of the user, device and operating system used to access the Site.The information we collect from these cookies and web beacons is used to determine information about a user’s visit to our Site, including the number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, navigation history through the website, and other statistics. This information is used to enhance the users experience while visiting our Site and to improve the performance of our Site by, among other things, allowing us to monitor Site performance, making the Site easier to use, measuring the effectiveness of promotional placements, and tailoring the Site (including the ads and offers a user receives) to better match a user’s interests and preferences.
Users who prefer not to accept cookies can set their Internet browser to notify them when they receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being placed on their hard drive.If you consent to our collection of cookies and you subsequently wish to withdraw your consent, you will need to manage the settings on your web browser to delete all cookies and disallow further acceptance of cookies. Please note that disabling cookies on your browser will prevent us from tracking your activities in relations to our Site, however, it may also disable some of the functions and features of the Site and the Site may not work properly.
By continuing to use our Site, you are agreeing to our placing cookies and/or web beacons on your computer in order to analyze the way you use our Site. Please read this cookie policy carefully for more details about the information we collect when you use the Site.
If you do not wish to accept cookies or web beacons in connection with your use of this Site, please discontinue use of the Site.
Use of Your Email Address
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and for future contact with you. Such addresses are not shared with third parties without your permission, except as required by law, to protect the SFA, its members, or the public, to share products and services of the SFA and its members, partners and sponsors, or with companies that help the SFA's fulfill its obligations to you. If you would like your email address removed from the SFA list, please contact SFA's Customer Service at membership@specialtyfood.com. NOTE: when you remove your email address from the list, you will not receive further updates regarding the Fancy Food Shows via email.
Links to other Websites
Please be aware that the Websites contain links to third-party websites, including websites of SFA members, which are not operated or controlled by the SFA. Such third-party websites may collect personally identifiable information from you. The SFA is not responsible for the privacy practices of such third-party websites, and such practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
Some portions of the Websites may be animated using downloadable applications and video which use hosting services operating under their own privacy and security policies.
Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to the SFA. We never collect or maintain information through the Websites from those we actually know are under the age of 18, except that we permit registered users under the age of 18 to maintain a personal dashboard or user profile under the supervision of a parent or guardian. No portion of the Websites is designed to attract anyone under the age of 18.
If we become aware that a person submitting personal information to us through the Websites is an unsupervised child, we promptly delete the information. A parent or guardian may request SFA to check for and delete any personal information of their child on SFA systems, or delete the personal dashboard of the child.
Your Acceptance of these Terms
By visiting or using the Websites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please exit the Websites immediately and do not visit or use the Websites in the future. This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, so please check back frequently.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or the use of your personal information by the SFA, please contact SFA Customer Service by email at membership@specialtyfood.com, by phone at (800) 627-3869; 212-482-6440, or by fax at 212-482-6459.
Close
Close
Message
Close
Login
Close
Share
